http://www.ucollege.edu/privacy-policy

Contact Union 402.486.2600ucinfo@ucollege.edu3800 S. 48th St.Lincoln, NE
68506 USAEnrollment Services 402.235.5529enroll@ucollege.eduAdmissions homepageAlumni/Giving 402.486.2503alumni@ucollege.eduAdvancement homepage Personnel directory ×
×Website Privacy Policy and Copyright NoticeUnion College values your privacy, and we are committed to protecting it.We will never sell or trade information you provide to us through our website, such as your e­mail, name, address or phone number. We may, on occasion, provide such information to a third party working for us on a contractual basis, on the condition that they also will protect your privacy and will not sell or disseminate your data.Some information is gathered automatically.Like most organizations with websites, Union College collects some data to determine how our site is used. Generic data is collected via “cookies,”­­ text files saved by your browser to evaluate usage patterns so we can evaluate content and patterns of behavior. You may turn off cookies by selecting the appropriate preferences in your Web browser. However, turning off cookies may affect the functionality of our websites. The information collected is based on your IP address, which gives the general location of your computer or network, but is not linked to any identifying data compiled by Union College, such as your email address or name. Union College will not associate your IP address with personally identifying information unless required to do so by law.Union College’s website uses Google Analytics to analyze and measure the usage of our websites. Google Analytics uses cookies to generate usage information, including your IP address, which is transmitted to Google and stored on its servers. Google may transfer this information to a third party when required to do so by law, or if the third party is used to process information on behalf of Google. Google Analytics will not associate your IP address with other data held by Google, and the data collected is displayed in aggregate without individually identifying information attached. By using this website, you consent to Google processing data about you as outlined above.To learn more about Google Analytics, please see their terms of use and Google’s privacy policies.Cookies are also used to serve targeted advertisements. After visiting this website, you may see ads for Union College on other websites. This is called “retargeting.” The information used by these ads to determine your interest in Union College is saved on your computer, not on a server. You may delete your cookies at any time to make the ads “forget” your interest.You may choose to provide us with information.To communicate effectively with you and other visitors to our website, Union College may ask for your personal information in online forms, such as requests to visit, inquiries about programs, applications for admissions, alumni address changes, and other information related to admissions, enrollment, campus services, alumni communication and other functions of Union College. Personal information gathered through these forms will never be sold, traded or otherwise shared with third parties without your consent or legal due process.Providing us with information is your choice. You may choose to use your browser in incognito or anonymous modes, which will limit our ability to track usage through cookies. Our website may not work correctly without certain essential routing or technical information, and failure to provide certain information or allow for cookies may mean features are not available to you.We are committed to data security.Whenever possible, Union College’s websites default to secure connections, meaning the data you transmit to us is encrypted. To know if you are using a secure connection, check the page URL for “https://” The “s” means “secure.”Union College strives to put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial safeguards to ensure the privacy and security of the data we collect online. We are committed to preventing unauthorized access, maintaining the accuracy of our data, and ensuring it is used ethically and legally.The scope of this policyThis policy applies to https://ucollege.edu, https://www.ucollege.edu, https://union.college and any other domain or subdomain that redirects to this website. Other policies may govern websites run by specific campus departments, student organizations and other affiliated groups using ucollege.edu subdomains. Many pages on this website contain links to external sites not owned by or affiliated with Union College. Union College is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of external sites.Changes to the policyUnion College reserves the right to change this policy at any time.Questions?For questions regarding the website or data collection, contact webmaster@ucollege.edu.Complaint ProcessIf you believe this site has violated your rights, including but not limited to your privacy, copyright or rights reserved to you under other applicable laws such as FERPA, you may contact us immediately to begin an informal complaint procedure. To ensure a prompt and thorough response, include in your message:Your name and the name of the organization you represent (if any)Contact information including an email address, mailing address and phone numberA URL linking to the offending contentA detailed description of the violation of your rights or applicable laws.Once a complaint is received, Union College’s webmaster will either take action or consult with the Web Committee and legal counsel to respond appropriately.To initiate a formal process, you must use the steps outlined in the relevant legislation. FERPA: file a complaint with the U.S. Department of EducationDMCA: to file a formal electronic copyright complaint, please notify the designated agent as per the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA), Public Law 105-304:Richard HenriquesDirector, Union College Information SystemsE-mail: CSHelp@ucollege.eduPhone: 402.486.2511U.S. Mail: 3800 S. 48th St. Lincoln, NE  68506 USAThe DMCA requires notification of claimed infringement be through written communication and contain: A physical or electronic signature of the copyright owner or a person authorized to act on their behalf.Identification of the work claimed to have been infringed upon.The location of the material with enough detail for Union College to find it.Contact information so the college can contact the individual issuing the complaint. (Please include mailing address, phone and email.)A statement that there is a good faith belief that the material addressed in the complaint has not be authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law.A statement that the information contained within the complaint is accurate and that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner under penalty of perjury. Individuals who use Union College's computers or network to infringe on copyright will be subject to disciplinary measures. Read more in the campus' digital copyright guidelines.CopyrightUnless otherwise noted, the content of the Union College website (such as text, graphics and photographs) belongs to Union College and was created as a work for hire.Redistribution and commercial use of this material is prohibited without the express permission of Union College. When you ask permission, please include your complete contact information and a description of how and where you will use the material.  Some text, images, video, music or other materials subject to copyright may be published on this website with the permission of the copyright holder. If you believe this website has infringed upon your rights, please see the complaint process detailed on this page.
Comment policy
About ...About Union CollegeAccreditationBoard of TrusteesCampus DescriptionCampus map: accessibility featuresCollege AdministrationCollege symbolsComment policyConsumer InformationContact UsDistance Learning Complaint Process for Out-of-State StudentsEmployee DirectoryEmploymentInteractive campus mapLincoln, NebraskaMission and visionNews from Union CollegeOur historySocial Media DirectoryWebsite Privacy Policy and Copyright NoticeWho are Seventh-day Adventists?HomeAbout Union CollegeAcademicsAdmissionsAdvancement OfficeCampus MinistriesCampus ServicesServices for ParentsStudent LifeStudent Success
